Carla: So, your sister is visiting from the US?
Ben: Yeah, she arrived late last night.
Carla: Is she staying with you?
Ben: No, she’s in a hotel.
My apartment’s too small.
Carla: Oh, OK.
She’s your twin, right?
That’s so cool.
Ben: Yeah… she’s going to meet Izzy this evening.
Carla: Cool!
Are you nervous?
Ben: Nervous?
Why?
Carla: I don’t know.
Your girlfriend is going to meet your family for the first time.
Ben: Well, it’s not all my family, just my sister.
Carla: Oh, well, fine.
Ben: Yeah, I mean… they’re very different,
but I’m sure they’re going to get on well.
Carla: Where are you going to meet?
Ben: Here, after Izzy finishes work.
Emma’s at the hotel now.
Carla: Oh, well, I look forward to meeting her!
Max: Hey Izzy, come and look at the new design.
Izzy: Sure!
Max: Listen, Izzy, are you free to go for a drink this evening?
Izzy: Oh, I… um… I’m sorry, I can’t.
Max: Oh no, it’s not just me – it’s everybody.
It’s a good chance to get to know the team.
Ola: Yeah, come on, Izzy.
We always have a great time.
Izzy: Thank you, Ola, but I can’t.
I’m meeting Ben and his sister this evening.
Ola: I think the Managing Director is going to be there.
Izzy:  Really?
Ola: Yeah, have you met him?
Izzy: No, I haven’t…
Maybe I can come later.
Max: Great. We’re meeting at the Red Lion.
Come when you can.